{
    "subject": "resource/Ken_Gatward",
    "predicate": "property/rank",
    "object": "resource/Group_captain",
    "human_readable": "Ken Gatward's rank is Group captain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8225517272949219,
            "question": "What is Ken Gatward's rank?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7653560638427734,
            "question": "Is Ken Gatward a high-ranking officer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6821418404579163,
            "question": "Are there any awards or honors associated with the rank of 'Group Captain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6750521063804626,
            "question": "Are there different levels within the rank of 'Group Captain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5459871888160706,
            "question": "What are some qualifications needed to achieve the rank of 'Group Captain'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4720367193222046,
            "question": "How does the rank of 'Group Captain' compare to 'Colonel'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41504576802253723,
            "question": "What does 'Group Captain' signify in the military?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3779291808605194,
            "question": "What branch of the military does Ken Gatward likely belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35469111800193787,
            "question": "What are the responsibilities of a Group Captain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12691551446914673,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other military ranks?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ken Gatward's rank is Group captain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2447_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the responsibilities of a Group Captain?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2447_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What branch of the military does Ken Gatward likely belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2447_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'Group Captain' signify in the military?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2447_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2447_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide evidence that Ken Gatward held various ranks, including Wing Commander and Group Captain. Specifically, it mentions that he retired on September 3, 1964, with the rank of Group Captain at the Air Cadet Headquarters at White Waltham. This supports the triple statement that Ken Gatward's rank is Group captain."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents explicitly mention that \"Group Captain Alfred Kitchener Gatward DSO DFC* AE\" was a British Royal Air Force (RAF) pilot. Additionally, the information provided states his rank was Group Captain after serving in the RAF for 30 years before retiring on 3 September 1964."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}